<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fundamental Compressor</string>
    <string name="launcher_app_name">Compressor</string>
    <string name="decompressor_label">Decompressor</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="error0">An error occurred.</string>
    <string name="error1">Error: Couldn\'t infer the file format from the file extension name or the MIME type.</string>
    <string name="error2">Error: The archive ‘%1$s’ is encrypted. A password is needed for extracting files out of it.</string>
    <string name="error3">Error: The second input password is different from the first one.</string>
    <string name="log">Log</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="compress">Compress</string>
    <string name="compressing">Compressing</string>
    <string name="compressing_with_ellipsis">Compressing…</string>
    <string name="decompress">Decompress</string>
    <string name="decompressing">Decompressing</string>
    <string name="decompressing_with_ellipsis">Decompressing…</string>
    <string name="extracting">Extracting</string>
    <string name="extracting_with_ellipsis">Extracting…</string>
    <string name="decompressing_and_extracting_with_ellipsis">Decompressing and extracting files…</string>
    <string name="archiving">Archiving</string>
    <string name="archiving_with_ellipsis">Archiving…</string>
    <string name="completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="file_has_been_selected">The following file has been selected:</string>
    <string name="folder_has_been_selected">The following folder has been selected:</string>
    <string name="file_is_being_compressed">The following file is being compressed:</string>
    <string name="file_is_being_decompressed">The following file is being decompressed:</string>
    <string name="file_is_being_unarchived">The following file is being unarchived:</string>
    <string name="folder_is_being_archived">The following folder is being archived:</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info1">The selected file will be decompressed.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info2">If checked, the result will be a ‘.tar’ file; if not checked, files and folders will be extracted from it.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info3">The file format is automatically inferred from the file extension name or its MIME type. If it is incorrect, you may correct it manually.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info4">This application is unable to create hard or symbolic links and can only replace them with placeholder files. Without using placeholder files, it will ignore links.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info5">When the file format is not specified and can\'t be inferred from its extension name or MIME type, this app will automatically infer this information from the file content. This function is highly unstable. It is recommended to explicitly select a file format instead.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info6">If the file names appear strange after decompression or unarchiving, it is likely that the encoding/decoding of the file names was incorrect. Overriding the encoding/decoding may solve this problem.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info7">The encoding of a file name in an archive is unrelated with that of its content. Overriding the file-name-decoding will not affect the files\' contents.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info8">Please select the output folder. All files will be extracted into this folder or its subfolders. This application will not create any additional folder when unarchiving an archive, which means all files that aren\'t recorded as having a parent directory in the archive will be written directly into the directory you select. Therefore, it is recommended that you choose an empty folder or manually create (and select) one for this app to access.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info9">Please use the system UI, which will be shown after you click the button, to pick the folder; the folder which you open is the folder you can select. The selected folder will only be used for this time, and this app will only have temporary access to it.</string>
    <string name="decompression_will_start1">Once you have chosen an output path, the decompression process will start.</string>
    <string name="decompression_will_start2">" Once the output path is chosen, the decompression process will start."</string>
    <string name="unarchiving_will_start">" Once the output path is chosen, the unarchiving process will start."</string>
    <string name="archiving_will_start">Once you have chosen an output path, the archiving process will start.</string>
    <string name="compression_will_start">Once you have chosen an output path, the compression process will start.</string>
    <string name="file_name_and_compressed_size">%1$s (Compressed size: %2$s)</string>
    <string name="file_or_dir_name_and_size">%1$s (Size: %2$s)</string>
    <string name="file_format">File format</string>
    <string name="unspecified">Unspecified</string>
    <string name="decompressor_option_decompress_only">Decompress only (without extracting)</string>
    <string name="decompressor_option_override_encoding">Override the encoding/decoding of the file names</string>
    <string name="decompressor_option_replace_links">Replace hard and symbolic links with placeholder files</string>
    <string name="select_input_file">Select the input file</string>
    <string name="select_input_folder">Select the input folder</string>
    <string name="file_compressor_info1">The selected file will be compressed. The output will be written into a new file. The original file will be preserved.</string>
    <string name="compression_format">Compression format</string>
    <string name="compression_or_archive_format">Compression or archive format</string>
    <string name="additional_compression_format">Additional compression format</string>
    <string name="encoding">Encoding</string>
    <string name="compressor_option_set_password">Set password</string>
    <string name="decompressor_option_use_password">Use password</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="note">Note</string>
    <string name="file_compressor_warning1">This mode is mainly used to make compressed non-archive files (such as .gz or .xz but not .tgz or .txz). It therefore can only compress one file at a time.</string>
    <string name="file_compressor_clickable_text1">If you intend to compress the entire folder, please click here.</string>
    <string name="show_advanced_options">Show advanced options</string>
    <string name="compression_level">Compression level</string>
    <string name="block_size">Block size</string>
    <string name="choose_output_path">Choose the output path</string>
    <string name="dir_compressor_info1">All files and subfolders (recursively, including the directory itself and subdirectories, the files under them, and the subdirectories of subdirectories…) in the selected folder will be compressed into a single archive file.</string>
    <string name="dir_compressor_option_create_tarball">Compress the result to create a tarball</string>
    <string name="documentation">Documentation</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="license_info_part1">"The source code of this app is available at "</string>
    <string name="license_info_part2">", under the MIT License."</string>
    <string name="doc_activity_button_show_libraries">See open source libraries used</string>
    <string name="show_open_source_libraries_activity_title">Open source libraries</string>
    <string name="space_parentheses_ignored">" (ignored)"</string>
    <string name="task_is_completed">The task is completed.</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="canceled">Cancelled</string>
    <string name="operation_is_canceled">The operation is cancelled.</string>
    <string name="doc_title1">1. Permissions</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_1">This part of the documentation describes how this app uses the app permissions. It describes the likely behaviours of a system running this app by the time this documentation is written. The actual behaviour may vary depending on the version of the system running this app.</string>
    <string name="doc_title1_1">i. The permission to post notifications</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_1_1">The permission for posting notification is only optional. It is used to log the names of files processed by this app. However, it isn\'t a required permission for this app to function.</string>
    <string name="doc_title1_2">ii. The permission to access files and directories</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_2_1">This app does NOT require the permission to write to the storage or the permission to manage all your files, as it only uses system APIs to access your files.\n\nWhen you select a file for this app to access, this app will be granted the temporary permission of reading that file. When you select a folder for creating an output file, this app will be granted the temporary permission to access a newly created file. Due to technical reasons, when you select a folder to compress, this app will be granted the temporary permission of managing files and subfolders (recursively) in that folder. The same also happens when you select a folder for extracting folders and files from an archive into it.\n\nThis app does not take the persistable permission of accessing a file or a directory you have chosen.</string>
    <string name="doc_title2">2. Usage</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_1">i. Compressing a file</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_1_1">This app has support for compressing a single file. It will be compressed using a compression-only, non-archiving format (of your choice). To do so, firstly choose a file, then choose the format and the output path, and after that, the chosen file will be compressed. Unlike some CLI programs you might have been using, this app doesn\'t delete the original file. (It has no permission to do that.)</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_2">ii. Archiving a folder</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_2_1">This app has support for archiving a folder, and optionally compress it if the archive format is archiving-only. (If it is not archiving-only, the output file will already be compressed.) To do so, firstly choose a folder, then choose the archive and optionally a compression format in addition (if supported), then choose the output path; all files and subfolders in that folder will be archived into a single archive file.</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_3">iii. Decompressing or extracting files</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_3_1">To decompress a compressed file, or to extract files from an archive file, firstly select the file; after that, the compression or archive format of that file will be automatically inferred; if it is incorrect, you may correct it. This app has support for only decompressing a compressed file that is also an archive of a certain format, without extracting files out of it, but this behaviour is optional. If you consider the format correct, or if you have corrected it, you should choose the output path; when the selected file is of a compression-only, non-archiving format, the output will be only one file, and you should choose the folder into which the output file should be written; otherwise, the output will be one or more files and/or directories extracted from the archive file, and you should choose the folder into which the output files should be written and directories should be created.</string>
    <string name="doc_title_appendix_1">Appendix I: Guessing the encoding</string>
    <string name="doc_text_appendix_1_1">If you see tofu-like unknown characters after decompressing or unarchiving a file, you might want to override the encoding/decoding of the decompression/unarchiving process to solve this problem. This part of the documentation describes how to choose the (more likely) correct decoding.\n\nIf the ZIP file you have is very ‘orthodox,’ it should use the IBM Code Page 437 for encoding the file name (but not its content); however, if its ‘language encoding flag’ is set, it should instead use UTF-8 as the encoding for file names. If the ZIP file isn\'t from a very old system, your best guess would be to override the encoding with UTF-8, and then, if it isn\'t successful (i.e. still producing unreadable characters like tofu), try UTF-16, and then, if it isn\'t successful, try overriding the file name encoding with your language\'s commonly used encoding (e.g. Shift_JIS for Japanese mixed script).</string>
</resources>