<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="error2">Error: The archive ‘%1$s’ is encrypted. A password is needed for extracting files out of it.</string>
    <string name="decompressor_info2">If checked, the result will be a ‘.tar’ file; if not checked, files and folders will be extracted from it.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="canceled">Cancelled</string>
    <string name="operation_is_canceled">The operation is cancelled.</string>
    <string name="doc_title1">1. Permissions</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_1">This part of the documentation describes how this app uses the app permissions. It describes the likely behaviours of a system running this app by the time this documentation is written. The actual behaviour may vary depending on the version of the system running this app.</string>
    <string name="doc_title1_1">i. The permission to post notifications</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_1_1">The permission for posting notification is only optional. It is used to log the names of files processed by this app. However, it isn\'t a required permission for this app to function.</string>
    <string name="doc_title1_2">ii. The permission to access files and directories</string>
    <string name="doc_text1_2_1">This app does NOT require the permission to write to the storage or the permission to manage all your files, as it only uses system APIs to access your files.\n\nWhen you select a file for this app to access, this app will be granted the temporary permission of reading that file. When you select a folder for creating an output file, this app will be granted the temporary permission to access a newly created file. Due to technical reasons, when you select a folder to compress, this app will be granted the temporary permission of managing files and subfolders (recursively) in that folder. The same also happens when you select a folder for extracting folders and files from an archive into it.\n\nThis app does not take the persistable permission of accessing a file or a directory you have chosen.</string>
    <string name="doc_title2">2. Usage</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_1">i. Compressing a file</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_1_1">This app has support for compressing a single file. It will be compressed using a compression-only, non-archiving format (of your choice). To do so, firstly choose a file, then choose the format and the output path, and after that, the chosen file will be compressed. Unlike some CLI programs you might have been using, this app doesn\'t delete the original file. (It has no permission to do that.)</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_2">ii. Archiving a folder</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_2_1">This app has support for archiving a folder, and optionally compress it if the archive format is archiving-only. (If it is not archiving-only, the output file will already be compressed.) To do so, firstly choose a folder, then choose the archive and optionally a compression format in addition (if supported), then choose the output path; all files and subfolders in that folder will be archived into a single archive file.</string>
    <string name="doc_title2_3">iii. Decompressing or extracting files</string>
    <string name="doc_text2_3_1">To decompress a compressed file, or to extract files from an archive file, firstly select the file; after that, the compression or archive format of that file will be automatically inferred; if it is incorrect, you may correct it. This app has support for only decompressing a compressed file that is also an archive of a certain format, without extracting files out of it, but this behaviour is optional. If you consider the format correct, or if you have corrected it, you should choose the output path; when the selected file is of a compression-only, non-archiving format, the output will be only one file, and you should choose the folder into which the output file should be written; otherwise, the output will be one or more files and/or directories extracted from the archive file, and you should choose the folder into which the output files should be written and directories should be created.</string>
    <string name="doc_title_appendix_1">Appendix I: Guessing the encoding</string>
    <string name="doc_text_appendix_1_1">If you see tofu-like unknown characters after decompressing or unarchiving a file, you might want to override the encoding/decoding of the decompression/unarchiving process to solve this problem. This part of the documentation describes how to choose the (more likely) correct decoding.\n\nIf the ZIP file you have is very ‘orthodox’, it should use the IBM Code Page 437 for encoding the file name (but not its content); however, if its ‘language encoding flag’ is set, it should instead use UTF-8 as the encoding for file names. If the ZIP file isn\'t from a very old system, your best guess would be to override the encoding with UTF-8, and then, if it isn\'t successful (i.e. still producing unreadable characters like tofu), try UTF-16, and then, if it isn\'t successful, try overriding the file name encoding with your language\'s commonly used encoding (e.g. Shift_JIS for Japanese mixed script).</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="license_info_part1">"The source code of this app is available at "</string>
    <string name="license_info_part2">", under the MIT Licence."</string>
</resources>